

CALLUM GILFEDDER

Cloud Specialist

DETAILS

Leighton Buzzard, LU7 4RX, Willing to relocate. callumgilf@mail.com +447704647533

PROFILE

Skilled mathematician placing in the top 10 students on the masters programme during the first semester of year 3. Subsequently being nominated to apply for a summer school at the London Mathematics Society. Experienced in many fields of mathematics with strengths in applied, pure and computational mathematics. 6 years (5 academic, 1 professional) of strong functional coding experience in Python (including experience with libraries such as Pandas, Numpy, Scipi, Matplotlib and more). Extensive experience with Microsoft Azure during my cloud specialist role at Go Deploy. Diligently created over 80 polished cloud tutorials aimed at IT professionals with a focus on Azure and GCP.

SKILLS

Advanced Analytical Thinking Skills	Python
Fast Learner	Azure
Programming	GCP
Computer Skills	AWS
Adaptability	Detail Oriented

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cloud Specialist, Go Deploy, Milton Keynes

SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

Underwent 3 months of cloud training, where I learnt the fundamentals of the major cloud platforms; Azure, AWS and GCP. Then branched out and took deeper studies into Azure. Successfully attained multiple Azure cloud certifications, such as:

- AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals.
- AI-900: Azure AI Fundamentals.
- DP-900: Azure Data Fundamentals.

Achieved the highest grades in the company with my DP-900 grade being 925/1000. This gives me a solid understanding of both Azure and AI/ML and data science. After completion of training, created and maintained a multitude of beginner to advanced level courses for cloud professionals. Expertly fulfilled

my main responsibility of creating Microsoft Azure cloud tutorials, by producing the highest quantity and quality of tutorials on my team, with a personal decision to focus on AI/ML and data science based tutorials. Additionally created a range of GCP tutorials. Created over 80 highly professional tutorials and responsibly managed over 300. Copiously populated the companies platform with a diverse range of high-quality tutorials. The titles of a sample of the stand-alone tutorials I created are:

- Create a Regression Model with Azure Machine Learning Designer.
- How to Connect to and Create a Secure Azure Machine Learning Workspace.
- Create and Connect to a PostgreSQL Instance using Azure.

Separate focus was also placed on non-cloud based tutorials. Independently taught myself the basics of programming languages such as R, Go, JavaScript, HTML and CSS as well as useful supplementary Python libraries such as TensorFlow and Pandas. Created full length courses aimed at providing the customer with a solid understanding of a larger topic than the stand-alone tutorials. Produced exemplary full-length courses on R, Go and Pandas.

Waiter, China Rose, Doncaster

MAY 2014 - AUGUST 2014

Waited tables for a high end Chinese restaurant. Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee. Working here led to the following needs and growth:

- Developed customer service skills.
- High stress environment requiring the ability to remain calm under pressure.
- Adapted to the needs of the customer.

Leaflet Distribution, Hayfield Academy, Doncaster

JULY 2014 - JULY 2016

Summer job delivering evening class leaflets to a wide area of Doncaster. This required careful pre-planning of delivery routes that was handled independently. Worked with a strong attention to detail and excellent record-keeping abilities. This developed and required:

- Planning and organizational abilities.
- Independence and initiative.
- Discipline to handle the long days on feet.

EDUCATION

Degree: Integrated Master's and Bsc (Hons) of Mathematics, University Of Leeds, Leeds

AUGUST 2017 - AUGUST 2021

Bachelors Dissertation: Computational Applied Mathematics.

• Successfully analysed the efficacy of computational methods for a multitude of applied problems. This is a highly transferable skill that can be applied to many professional practices.

Master's Dissertation: Periodic solutions of the N-body problem.

- Independently developed a computational technique for measuring a quantity of vital importance to
 my topic that I then optimized twice. Improving it's performance by a factor of 1000-10000% depending
 on the circumstances.
- Numerically simulated solar system dynamics for long-term stability forecasting and extrapolation.
 Displaying considerable ability in dealing with exceedingly complicated topics with a rigorous and scientific attention to detail.

<u>Modules Included</u>: General Relativity. Entropy. Linear and Non-linear Waves. Advanced Mathematical Methods. Statistics. Logic. Financial Mathematics 1 - 3. Analysis. Topology and Geometry. Computational Mathematics.

A levels: A* Maths, A Further Maths, B Chemistry, Hayfield Academy, Doncaster

JULY 2014 - JULY 2016

GCSE's: 3A*'s, 4A's, 4B's and a C., Hayfield Academy, Doncaster

JULY 2011 - JULY 2014

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Manchester and Hull Marathon's, Manchester

APRIL 2018 - APRIL 2018

Raised approximately £300 each for Cancer Research UK and the Batten Disease Family Association while independently organizing the advertising for donations. Exhibited excellent self-discipline and self-management skills. Rigorously planned training regiment and stuck to it diligently. Then successfully completed the difficult task that is a marathon. With the fastest time being around 4 and a half hours.

Youtube Channel, Doncaster

JANUARY 2014 - JULY 2017

Created a You-tube channel that gathered a community of around 300 people viewing the content on a regular basis. With videos attaining up to a couple thousand views. This skills I developed during this time were:

- Clean and professional digital art and design skills, that was used to create strong thumbnails that would intrigue the viewer to click onto the video.
- Gained experience with several video editing software, and successfully edited the videos to a highly professional and aesthetic standard.
- Developed speaking and communication skills that were required to entertain the audience who viewed the videos, and entertained/communicated with the audience leading to at least 300 people subscribed to the content.

Online Art Portfolio, Doncaster

AUGUST 2013 - OCTOBER 2014

Developed an online art portfolio that gathered 100 followers that regularly viewed my content. This brought forth excellent creative thinking abilities and skills.

HOBBIES

Exercise and fitness. Weightlifting. Creating, editing and publishing videos. Piano playing. Physics and cosmology. Avid reader of philosophy, specifically metaphysics, epistemology and ethics. Badminton and tennis.